Hi.
Hey.
So, I'm in my apartment doing
the Soap Opera Digest
crossword puzzle
and guess who is the clue
for three down?
Hmm, "Three, down--
Days of Our Lives star
'blank' Tribbiani."
That's me! I'm "blank!"
Uh-huh.
Hey.
How cool is this?
We know three down.
I'm touching
three down.
Yeah, you are, baby.
Three down knows
I'm married.
What's three
down doing?
Did they call you to tell you
your name's going to be in this?
No. They really like me
over there, though.
They wanted to do a big profile
on me, but I said no.
Why'd you say no?
Remember what happened
the last time
I did an interview for them?
I said I write a lot
of my own lines
and then the
writers got mad
and made my character fall down
the elevator shaft?
So, who knows what
I might say this time.
If only there was
something in
your head
to control the
things you say.
Oh, come on
Joey, you will totally keep it
in check this time.
And plus, the
publicity
would be really good
for your career.
And you deserve that.
And if you do the interview,
you could mention...
oh, I don't know,
"galpal Rachel Green"?
Is that "galpal"
spelled L-O-S-E-R?
Don't listen to
him. Please?
Fine, all right,
I'll do it.
But hey-- you guys
have to be at the next table
so you can stop me
if I, you know, start to say
something stupid.
Just then, or-or all the time?
'Cause we have jobs, you know?
Come on, we will be there
for you the whole time.
Just remember,
"galpal Rachel Green."
( giggles )
I'm going to be
in Soap Opera Digest!
And not just in the dumb
crossword puzzle.
Seriously,
proud of you.
Yeah.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
I really appreciate
you taking the
time to do this.
Oh, not at all-- happy to do it.
Do you think
we're being obvious?
No, we're just
four people
with neck problems
who talk like this.
I think it's great that
you wanted to meet here.
You know, when most people hear
that the magazine
is paying for it
they want to go
to a big, fancy restaurant.
Actually, I didn't know
the magazine was paying.
Wouldn't have mattered.
I'm doing this for the fans,
not for the free food.
( chuckling )
Can I get you anything?
Um, I'll have a
cup of coffee.
And, uh, I'll have
all the muffins.
Hey.
Shh.
We're not talking.
Oh, finally.
( sighs )
So, according to your bio
you've done quite a bit of work
before Days of Our Lives.
Anything that you're
particularly proud of?
( with German accent ):
♪ All you vant is a dinkle ♪
♪ Vat you envy's a scwhang ♪
♪ A thing through which
you can tinkle ♪
♪ Or play with,
or simply let hang ♪
( piano interlude )
Folks, this ever happen to you?
You go to the
refrigerator
to get a nice
glass of milk
but these darn
cartons are
so flingin'
flangin' hard
to open!
Well, you said it, Mike.
Oh, oh.
There's got to be
a better way.
And there is, Kevin.
This is his first time.
He's never used this
product before.
You'll see how easy
this is to do. Go ahead.
( popping )
This works in
any milk carton.
Oh, it is easy.
Now I can have milk...
every day.
( audience oohs and ahs )
So, this is it, Victor?
Yeah, I guess it is.
And so...
I'm going to get on
this spaceship...
( science fiction
sound effects )
( engine revs )
And I'm going to
go to Blargon 7
in search of
alternative fuels.
But when I return...
200 years from now?
You'll be long gone.
But I won't have
aged at all.
So you tell your great,
great granddaughter
to look me up.
Because Adrian, baby...
I'm going to want
to meet her.
( science fiction
sound effects )
Shh, Shh. Okay, here
I come, here I come.
See, I'm coming
to fix the copier.
I can't get to the copier.
I'm thinking,
"What do I do, what do I do?"
( sounds of passion )
So I just watch them have sex.
And then I say--
wait, here's my line.
JOEY:
You know, that's bad
for the paper tray.
Nice work,
my friend.
Thank you. Wait, wait, wait,
you see me again.
Hang on, the guy's butt's
blocking me.
There I am. There I am.
There I am.
Oh, well, there's
so many things
it's hard
to pick just one.
I'm going to get
some coffee.
Does anyone want anything?
Oh, yeah,
I'd actually love
a blueberry muffin,
and a chamomile tea.
Uh, double latte,
extra foam.
And a bagel
with only a...
I was just being polite.
Okay, how about when
you're not working?
What do you do in
your spare time?
( foghorn blows )
Look at this clown.
Just because he
got a bigger boat
he thinks he can take
up the whole river.
Get out of the
way, jackass!
Who names their boat
Coast Guard, anyway?
That is the Coast Guard.
What are they
doing out here?
The coast is all
the way over there.
Hey.
Check it out.
This is
unbelievable.
Joey has been
holding his breath
for almost four minutes.
Dude, what--
you trying to kill me?
Well, I see you've had
a very productive day.
Don't you think the cowboy
hat's a little much?
Come on, it's fun.
All right.
Isn't this a woman's hat?
Dude, stop talking crazy
and make us some tea.
You know what?
Huh?
We have to turn off the porn.
I think you're right.
( moaning )
All right, ready?
BOTH:
One, two, three.
That's kind of nice.
Yeah, that's kind of a relief.
Yeah.
( sighs )
You want to see
if we still have it?
Yeah.
Free porn!
We have free porn!
Yes! Yes!
In my spare time,
I read to the blind
and I'm also
a mento for kids.
A "mento?"
Yeah, you know, a mento--
a role model.
A "mento"?
Right.
Like the candy?
As a matter of fact, I do.
( chuckles )
Well, another thing that
our readers always
want to know
is how soap stars stay
in such great shape.
Do you have some kind
of a fitness regime?
Uh, we stars usually
just try to eat right
and get lots
of exercise.
Wow, you realize we've
been throwing this ball
without dropping it
for, like, an hour?
Are you serious?
Yeah, I realized it
a half hour ago
but I didn't want
to say anything
because I didn't want
to jinx it.
Oh.
Wow, we are pretty good at this.
Yeah.
Hey, we totally forgot
about lunch.
I think that's the first time
I've ever missed a meal.
Yeah-- I think my pants
are a little loose.
What's wrong with you?
Well, I got this blinding
pain in my stomach
when I was lifting
weights before
and then I, uh, passed out.
And uh, haven't been able
to stand up since.
( chuckles ):
But, uh, I don't think it's
anything serious.
This sounds like a hernia.
You have to...
you-you go to the doctor.
No way! Hey, look,
if I'm going to go
to the doctor for anything,
it's going to be
for this thing sticking out
of my stomach!
Eww...
I'm going to have to start
working out again.
Damn you fifteens!
What is it?
It's a trifle.
It's got all
of these layers.
First, there's a layer
of ladyfingers
then a layer of jam.
Then custard...
which I made from scratch.
Mmm.
Then raspberries,
more ladyfingers
then beef sautéed with peas
and onions
more custard...
It tastes like feet.
I like it.
Are you kidding?
What's not to like?
Custard? Good. Jam? Good.
Meat? Good.
Well, you... you don't look
good, Joe.
Well, the fridge broke,
so I had to eat everything.
Cold cuts, ice cream, limes.
Hey, what was in that brown jar?
That's still in there?
Not anymore.
Hey, look.
There's a piece that
doesn't have floor on it.
Stick to your side!
Come on, now.
All right, what are we having?
Uh, I don't believe in these
crazy diets, you know?
Just everything in moderation.
Your muffins.
Uh...
I'll take those to go.
For the kids.
( chuckles )
Oh, I know what I
wanted to ask you.
You were on the
show years ago
and then they
killed you off.
What happened there?
Oh, it's so stupid.
I said some stuff
in an interview
that I really
shouldn't have said.
But believe me, that is not
going to happen today.
( laughter )
Understood.
So, what'd you say back then?
Oh, I said that I...
( all shouting at once )
Hey, man, what's up?
What's happening?
Hi.
You guys,
this is Shelly.
She's interviewing me
for Soap Opera Digest.
Shelly, these are
my friends.
Hi. I'm gal-pal
Rachel Green.
Um, and, uh,
if you want the dirt
I'm the one you come to.
This might be Joey's baby.
Who knows?
( laughing ):
I'm just kidding.
Seriously,
gal-pal, Rachel Green.
Who just lost the respect
of her unborn child.
Um, I'm going to just go
get this warmed up.
Okay.
Joey, you're doing great.
Yeah, so far,
nothing stupid.
"Mento"?
No, thanks.
So, as Joey's friends
is there anything that you guys
think our readers ought to know?
Uh, no, just, just
that he is a great guy.
( scoffs ):
Yeah.
That's going to get you
into Soap Opera Digest.
Well, I, well, oh...
I would just like to say
that Joey truly has enriched
the days of our lives.
Um, I, I just think
that you don't expect
someone so hot to be so sweet.
SHELLY:
Ooh...
I like that.
Oh.
What's your name?
Um, Phoebe Buffay.
How do you spell that?
So we can get it right.
Oh, okay, it's, um,
"P" as in "Phoebe"
"H" as in "Heebee,"
"O" as in "O-bee"
"E" as in "Eebee"
"B" as in "Beebee"
and "E" as in
"'Ello, there, mate."
SHELLY ( chuckling ):
Great.
Well, it was nice
meeting all of you.
Yeah, you, too.
You, too.
JOEY:
Thanks, you guys.
MONICA:
Bye.
So it seems like you
have a lot of friends.
Who would you say is
your best friend?
JOEY:
Ooh...
How come you have two?
Well, this one's for you.
Get out.
No, I can't.
No, no, listen
I know how much
this means to you
and I also know that this is
about more than just jewelry.
It's about you and me
and the fact that we're
"best buds."
Wow.
Is this friendship?
I think so.
Check it out.
We're bracelet buddies.
That's what they'll call us.
( TV plays )
Oh! Joey...
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's all right.
Don't worry about it.
Oh, no, but look.
Aah, that's going
to leave a stain.
Rach, hey, it's fine.
You're at Joey's.
Really?
Yeah, look.
Huh.
Yeah.
I've never lived
like this before.
I know.
Whoo!
( laughing )
All right, well,
don't waste it.
I mean,
it's still food, jeez.
I've been feeling
incredibly guilty
about this
because I want to be
a good friend
and damn it, I am a good friend
so just-just shut up
and close your eyes.
Yeah, uh...
Wow.
You are a good friend.
Of course,
the audition was this morning
and I didn't get it.
But that was a hell of a kiss.
Rachel is a very lucky girl.
Let's get the contestants
out of their isolation booths.
And, they're off.
( clucking )
Whoa.
Get your foot
off my contestant. Judge.
Judge rules...
No violation.
Aw.
And the duck gets
a Nutter Butter!
No!
Oh, hey, that's not
a Nutter Butter.
That's just an old wanton.
Well, judge rules...
Nutter Butter.
Oh...
Tough call.
Yeah.
I'd seen this thing
on the Discovery Channel.
Wait a minute.
I saw that
on the Discovery Channel.
Yeah, about jellyfish,
and how if you...
Eww!
You peed on yourself?
You can't say that.
You-you don't know!
I mean, I thought
I was going to pass out
from the pain.
Anyway, I-I, I tried
but I-I couldn't...
bend that way.
So?
Eww! Eww! Eww!
That's right, I stepped up.
She's my friend,
and she needed help.
If I had to,
I'd pee on any one of you.
Um, nope. No best friend, no.
Just, uh,
a lot of close friends, yeah.
So, um, now back
to the show...
How does it feel to have
a huge gay fan base?
Really?
Me?
Wow. I don't even know
any huge gay people.
It hurts me.
It physically hurts me.
Now, off the record
you're not...?
What? Are you referring
to my man's bag?
At first, I thought it
just looked good
but it's practical, too.
Check it out.
It's got compartments
for all your stuff.
Your wallet, your keys,
your address book...
Your makeup.
Now, now, now, should I
climb down your front
so we're face-to-face
or-or should I climb down
your back
so we're-we're... butt-to-face?
Face-to-face. I...
Face-to-face, yeah.
Okay, here I come.
All right.
Oh, my...
( straining ):
How much do you weigh, Ross?
I prefer not to answer
that right now.
I'm still carrying
a little holiday weight.
( grunts )
Oh...
You know, when we talked
about face-to-face
I don't think we thought it
all the way through.
Hey, Pheebs.
Hey.
Check it out.
Huh?
How much of a man am I?
Wow. Nice.
Manly, and also kind of a slut.
You're turning into a woman.
No, I'm not.
Why would you say that?
That's just mean.
Now I've upset you?
What did I say?
Not what you said;
it's just the way you said it.
Oh, my God!
I'm a woman!
( sniffs )
Mmm. Great nap.
It really was.
( chuckles )
( clears throat )
Uh, me? Gay? No. No. No.
Uh, but I have a number
of close friends who are.
So, then let's talk
about women.
I'm sure our female readers
will be interested to know
about your romantic life.
Oh, oh, well, what I do is, uh
I look a woman up and down
and I say, "Hey, how youdoin'?"
Oh, please.
Hey, how you doin'?
( giggles )
Hey... how you doin'?
He has the most amazing Porsche
under there.
I'd love to show you,
but I just tucked her in.
She's sleeping.
( both giggle )
Hey, uh, would you two girls
like to go for a drink?
Is Rachel here?
I'm her sister.
Oh, my God! Jill!
Oh, my God! Rachel!
Oh!
( mockingly ):
Oh, my God! Introduce us.
Well, this is Chandler.
Hi. Hi.
And you know
Monica and Ross.
And that's Phoebe.
And that's Joey.
Hey, how you doin'?
Don't!
You're a really nice guy
and I'm happy to be
your roommate
and your friend
I'm just, you know,
I just...
don't feel that
way about you.
Oh. I see what happened.
It's because I was trying
to repel you. Right?
Believe me, you'd feel
a lot different
if I turned it on.
I don't think so.
Oh, I do.
How you doin'?
I'm okay.
( voice breaks ):
Well...
Oh, dear God!
Well, not much to tell there.
I'm... really shy.
So, that's it.
I guess that's all I need.
Thank you, so much.
I think they will be
running this
in the beginning of next month.
Oh, great.
Great.
Thank you.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
I did it.
Amazing.
Yeah.
Oh, wait. I almost forgot.
We have to ask everybody this.
Other than Days of Our Lives
what's your favorite soap opera?
Oh...
I don't watch soap operas.
Excuse me, I have a life.
( chuckling ):
You know?
Thank you.
The readers at Soap Opera Digest
will be happy to learn that.
Oh, good enough.
So close.
Wow, I can't believe
they didn't put in the part
where you said
you didn't watch soap operas.
Yeah, I called the lady
about that.
I told her I was just joking.
She was pretty nice about it.
You slept with her,
didn't you?
Little bit, yeah.
Wow. This picture
of you sure is steamy.
Oh, yeah, that's
just a little something
for my huge gay fan base.
Did you just wink at me?
Hey, you're the one
who loves the picture.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org